Contact

Dankuni, Hooghly - 712311 8116555423 (Mobile) asifstar135@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/md-asif-mondal-20555421b (LinkedIn) asifstar786.github.io/AsifStar/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Amazon Web Services (AWS)
Tailwind CSS
Problem Solving

MD ASIF MONDAL

FullStack Dev @Ditinex | Knight @Leetcode(1870+)| CSE'24 Kolkata, West Bengal, India

Summary

Hello! Myself MD Asif Mondal, a Computer Science student of 3rd year. I am a software enthusis and creative minded student and interested to learn new technologies day by day. I am a expert C++ coder and do solve DS & Algo problems on leetcode, GFG and other platforms consistently. Besides these, I am a fronted developer and have worked on several WebApp projects. Currently I am open to join a good IT company as a intern and showcase my talent with these techStacks as well as learn new technologies. My future aim is to get placed in top MNC's with a SDE or other technical profile and give my 100% there.

Experience

Ditinex
Full Stack Developer
November 2023 - Present (7 months)
Kolkata, West Bengal, India

Nashbud Back End Development intern March 2023 - November 2023 (9 months) Remote

GDSC Aliah
DSA mentor
November 2022 - November 2023 (1 year 1 month)
Helped 100+ college juniors in their DSA journey. #

Education

Aliah University, Kolkata Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2020 - 2024)

Dhaniakhali Mahamaya Vidyamandir

High School Diploma, Pure Science · (August 2018 - March 2020)